Your closest store based on
---------------------------

 Update

, ,

### Regular Hours:

Get Directions

* Brands

* Brands

* Brands

* Brands

* Ways to Shop

* Small Space Living Room Furniture

* Small Space Dining Furniture

* Small Space Bedroom Furniture

* Small Space Office Furniture

[Log in](https://www.thebrick.com/account/login)* Or

* Inspiration

* Services

Promotion Details Détails de la promotion

Seller Name

Privacy Policy
==============

Quick Links
-----------

**Our Promise and Who We Are**

**What, how and why do we collect, use and disclose?**

**How do we protect your Personal Information?**

Our Promise and Who We Are
--------------------------

### Our Promise to Our Valued Customers

The Brick Group cares about its customers and, as part of that concern, appreciates that its customers care about how their personal information is handled by The Brick Group. Our goal is to make your shopping experience for furniture, mattresses, appliances and home electronics, and the financing of these products, the very best we can. This goal includes keeping your information secure, and to collect, use and disclose your information only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

The Brick Group promises to abide by this Privacy Policy and to deal with all personal information in a responsible, professional and respectful manner. In the unusual circumstance that we fall short of these goals, The Brick Group promises to make every effort to address and resolve your concerns in an appropriate, fair and timely manner.

### Who We Are

“The Brick Group” as used in this Privacy Policy includes Leon’s Furniture Limited, The Brick Ltd., The Brick Warehouse LP (including its general partner), United Furniture Warehouse LP (including its general partner United Furniture Warehouse (a division of The Brick Warehouse LP)), , The Brick Mattress Store (a division of The Brick Warehouse LP), Trans Global Warranty Corp., Trans Global Life Insurance Company, Trans Global Insurance Company, Trans Global Services (a division of The Brick Warehouse LP), Midnorthern Appliance (a division of The Brick Warehouse LP), First Oceans Hong Kong Limited and First Oceans Trading Corporation as well as our franchised locations.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, we, us and our mean The Brick Group, and you and your mean a customer or prospective customer of The Brick Group.

What, how and why do we collect, use and disclose?
--------------------------------------------------

### Personal Information

Personal information is information about an identifiable individual, excluding an employee’s name, title and business address and business phone number. Your personal information includes, but is not limited to, your contact information and your financial information. If you are making a claim under your credit insurance with either Trans Global Insurance Company or Trans Global Life Insurance Company, personal information will also include health information.

### The Purposes of Collection, Use and Disclosure

We collect, use and disclose your personal information only for identified purposes with your knowledge and consent. We always collect, use and disclose your personal information reasonably and for reasonable purposes. This Policy applies to our interactions with our customers and visitors including but not limited to the use of our websites and mobile websites; visits to our stores or attendance at one of our events; when making a purchase from us at our retail stores on online through our website; use of our applications for mobile phones, tablets or other smart devices; communications including telephone, text and email communications; social media interactions on our websites and other third-party websites like Facebook, Youtube, Pinterest, Google+, TikTok, Instagram and Twitter, visits to our online advertisements or emails and through our authorized service providers.

### Personal Information we Collect

We collect and use your personal information in order to provide you with the products you purchase from us, to collect payment from you, to effect delivery or pick-up of the products (if applicable), to issue and administer gift and promotional cards, and in order to provide follow-up customer service and, warranty service, financing, or credit insurance on those products (if applicable). We also collect this information to process and track returns and credits and to help detect and prevent fraud and otherwise administer our loss prevention program.

When you make a purchase from us, we will ask you for your name, home address and phone number. For any online transaction we will also collect your email address. Although you are not required in every circumstance to give us this information to complete your purchase, should you choose not to provide it to us we will be impeded in assisting you if you have problems or concerns with your purchase in the future, particularly if you do not retain your sales invoice.

If you make a purchase using a Credit Card, we collect your name, billing address for the card, type of card, card number and card expiration date. We require this information in order to process your purchase.

If you are applying for a Credit Card, in addition to your name, address and phone number, and your email address if you provide it to us, we, on our own behalf and as agent for Flexiti or to such other financing provider we may refer you, collect additional personal information and/or financial information as required on the application form in order to process your application and for the purposes set out in this policy, the Credit Card application, the cardholder agreement for the Credit Card. Please refer to Flexiti’s Privacy Policy found at [www.flexiti.com/EN/Privacy](https://www.thebrick.com/pages/www.flexiti.com/EN/Privacy).

If we are delivering your purchase to you, we require your name, address for delivery and phone number. If you will be picking up your purchase at a later time, we require your name and other identifying personal information in order to verify your identity as the purchaser at the time of pick-up.

When at all possible, we collect your personal information directly from you. If you are applying for a Credit Card, we and/or Flexiti and its affiliates may collect additional personal information and/or financial information from third parties such as a credit bureau.

If you register in one of our programs or enter a contest or promotion, we collect your personal information to administer your participation in the program, contest or promotion. We also may collect information including photos, videos and other content if you choose to upload the information or post a review, which may be viewed by others. We also may use this information to inform you about products, promotions and services that we think may interest you unless you advise us that you do not wish to receive such information.

In order to improve your customer experience, we use third-party analytics services which may include monitoring social media, search engine and email distribution services to assist us in analyzing trends in our services. In using these analytics services, we generate and process aggregated information that does not review your identity. If we combine or connect aggregated information to your Personal Information, which may allow us to directly or indirectly identify you, we will treat this information as Personal Information and will be administered in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We disclose your personal information to our suppliers to provide warranty, financing, credit and other services on the products you purchase. When we offer special promotions by which you receive one or more free goods or services directly from one of our suppliers, we disclose your personal information to those suppliers for them to contact you to arrange for provision of their goods and/or services and for follow-up service.

If you are applying for or financing your purchase using a Flexiti Credit Card, issued by Flexiti Financial Inc. (“Flexiti”), we collect, use and disclose your information including personal information and/or financial information, on our own behalf and as agent for Flexiti and their affiliates for the purposes set out in this Policy, the Credit Card application, the cardholder agreement for the Credit Card and Flexiti’s Privacy Agreement found at [www.flexiti.com/EN/Privacy](https://www.thebrick.com/pages/www.flexiti.com/EN/Privacy). The Brick may be providing Customer Service on the Credit Card Accounts for Flexiti and The Brick may share your information including personal, financial and/or transaction information with each other and with their affiliates or others for that purpose and as described in this Policy.

We may offer additional financing programs through The Brick or other third-party financing providers from time to time. If you choose one of these financing programs, we will collect, use and disclose your information including personal information and/or financial information on our own behalf and as agent for the financing provider and may share your information including personal and transaction information with the financing provider.

If you make a claim pursuant to your credit insurance purchased through either Trans Global Life Insurance Company or Trans Global Insurance Company, we will collect and use your health information to process your claim.

We collect, use and disclose as little of your personal information as we can while still ensuring that we can fulfill our identified purposes. We never sell or trade your personal information to any person or organization outside of The Brick Group.

We may also capture your image with closed circuit cameras when you visit our stores to prevent and detect fraud and otherwise as part of our loss prevention program. We may require you to authenticate your identity for verification purposes.

We may get information about you from third-party business partners such as updated shipping information. We may also collect information about you from a friend or relative. If you refer someone to us, please ensure that you only submit contact information of individuals with whom you have a close personal or family relationship who would be interested in receiving communications from us or who have authorized you to share their contact information.

We otherwise collect, use and disclose your personal information as permitted and/or required by law.

### Consent

We imply your consent to collect, use and disclose your personal information for the reasonable and necessary purposes set out above. If, at any time, we wish to collect, use and/or disclose your personal information for any other purpose, we will notify you of that purpose and seek your consent to do so.

Please also note that, in some limited circumstances, we are permitted by law to collect, use and/or disclose your personal information without your consent, with or without notice to you.

### Cookies and Non-Identifying Information

The Brick Group uses both session cookies (which are automatically deleted from your computer when you close your browser session) and persistent cookies (which remain on your computer between sessions) in order to facilitate your ability to use the website efficiently and effectively. By using our website while your browser is set to accept cookies, we imply your consent to them.

If you are browsing or shopping online, we and/or our trusted third-party agents track your movement through our website and collect statistics about your navigation, such as page views and time spent on the website, using click stream data and tag software. This information about your visit to our website is then aggregated with the information about other individuals’ visits. Using this non-identifying information, we strive to continually improve and enhance the online experience of all of our customers, to evaluate the success of marketing campaigns and to report on aggregated site usage. In no case is click stream data or tag software used by us to collect or store personally identifiable information.

### How do we use your personal information?

We use the information we collect for our business purposes including processing purchases, completing orders, ensuring proper delivery and pick-up, responding to inquiries, responding to product and service inquiries and reviews, and administering your participation in a contest, promotion or program. We also may use your information to process product returns, warranty claims and credits, and to inform you of product recalls.

We may use your information to improve our product and service offerings and our website. We may also use your information to customize your experience with us. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we have received from third parties or which may be publicly available to assess trends and interests.

We may use your information to protect our business, our customers, our employees and our websites for security and fraud detection purposes. We may use your ID and personal information for authentication and verification purposes. Information collected in the course of serving you may be used to help detect and prevent fraud and otherwise administer our loss prevention program.

We may contact you to tell you about changes to our Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use of our websites or mobile applications or changes to any of our programs which you may have enrolled. We may also contact you about any issues with your order including any advisories or product recalls.

We also use your personal information to inform you of products, services and promotions that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also collect information about products or services you like, reviews you submit or where you shop, as well as information like your age and gender. If you use our mobile websites or applications, we may collect location data obtained from your mobile device or from your IP address. We use this location information to find the nearest store to you, to provide you with product pricing and availability and to provide you with directions. Some mobile applications may use this information to determine if you are shopping or otherwise located near or in one of our locations. Although we believe these services are a benefit to our customers, we understand that you may not wish to receive such unsolicited information, in which case you may simply contact us (please see below) and advise us of same. If you have received such information via email you do not wish to continue receiving, you may submit an electronic request to be removed from our mailing lists or if you received such information by way of an automated telephone message, you may request to be removed from our automated notification calling list by calling the toll free telephone number provided in the message and entering your phone number.

When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking websites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain social media account information as determined by the settings of the social media services to deliver the contact or as part of the operation of the website, plug-in or application. Social media platforms may collect information about your use of our services and may notify other uses of the platform about your activities on our websites and mobile applications. Your interactions with social media features are governed by the respective privacy policies of the companies providing the features.

How do we protect your Personal Information?
--------------------------------------------

### Transmission, Storage and Retention

The security of your personal information is very important to us. If you are transmitting information to us electronically, all of your personal information is encrypted (or coded) through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol, and is only decoded when it reaches our servers.

We have policies and procedures in place to ensure that your personal information, both in electronic and paper format, is kept safe and secure, and we impress upon our employees the importance of maintaining the highest standards of ethics and confidentiality.

### Destruction

Personal information you provide to us is purged from our systems and records after seven (7) years, being a reasonable period of time following expiration of any warranties and other obligations we might have to you and/or to public bodies.

### How can you control your personal information?

You may contact us at any time (please see below) if you wish to access, verify or correct your personal information in our possession, or if you wish to amend or withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information pursuant to this Privacy Policy or otherwise.

Please note that, if you choose not to provide personal information to us, or if you choose not to consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information according to this Privacy Policy, our ability to serve you, both now and in the future, may be impeded. In that case, we will advise you of the repercussions necessarily flowing from your choice in order to empower you to make an informed decision.

### What if we revise this Privacy Policy?

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy periodically without notice, and any such revisions will be posted on our website. You may also obtain a paper copy of this Privacy Policy by contacting us (please see below). We encourage you to consult this Privacy Policy regularly in order to remain informed of any changes that may impact you and affect our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.

### Where can you contact Us?

If, at any time, you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or any questions or concerns about your personal information that we hold, please contact us at:

**THE BRICK**  
16930 - 114 Avenue  
Edmonton, Alberta  
T5M 3S2  
Attention: Chief Privacy Officer  
Phone: 1-866-508-7766 (toll free)  
Fax: 780-454-0969  
Email: [Privacy@TheBrick.com](mailto:privacy@thebrick.com)

Our Chief Privacy Officer, or an appropriate delegate, will review your communication and, if necessary, respond to you directly.

Sign up to receive our emails
-----------------------------

You can unsubscribe at any time.

Join the Conversation
---------------------

Customer Service
----------------

Company Information
-------------------

We accept:

* 
* 
* 
* 
* 

Prices on this website are for online purchases only. Prices in-store may differ.

Product and service availability, pricing, selection and promotional offers may vary by location and may not be exactly as illustrated. We reserve the right to limit quantities by store and per purchase. To receive bonus offer or discount, complete package must be purchased and kept. + This offer cannot be combined with any other discount or free gift purchase, sale, or other promotion, unless otherwise specified.

TheBrick.com is a division of The Brick Warehouse LP 2004 - 2024 . The Brick Warehouse LP. All Rights Reserved.

The Brick started in 1971 as a single furniture store in downtown Edmonton, Alberta. 50 years later, you can shop with us online or at one of our 200+ locations and distribution centres across Canada from Victoria to St. Johns.

Sign up to receive emails from The Brick.

       Enter Email     

Sign Up for promotional emails from The Brick Group. You can withdraw your consent at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in your email. See our [Privacy Policy](https://www.thebrick.com/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy") or [Contact Us](https://www.thebrick.com/contact-us "Contact Us") for more details on changing your marketing preferences for The Brick Group. See full [contest details](https://www.thebrick.com/pages/contests#ebrick "Contests").
